<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="interop_consent_body" translatable="false" />
    <!-- XHED: Header of private data in the delta onboarding interoperability view -->
    <string name="interoperability_onboarding_delta_footerTitle" translatable="false">"Information on data processing"</string>
    <!-- XTXT: Description of private data in the delta onboarding interoperability view. Below interoperability_onboarding_delta_footerTitle -->
    <string name="interoperability_onboarding_delta_footerDescription" translatable="false">"You do not need to change anything to find out whether you have had possible exposures involving app users in the participating countries and are therefore at risk of infection yourself. You just need to make sure that the exposure logging feature is still enabled. Exposure logging will automatically warn you about any possible exposure you had with a user of the Corona-Warn-App or any other official coronavirus app.\n\nWhen COVID-19 Exposure Notifications are enabled, your Android smartphone continuously generates random IDs and sends them via Bluetooth so that they can be received by other smartphones near you. Your Android smartphone, in turn, receives the random IDs of other smartphones. Your own random IDs and those received from other smartphones are recorded by your Android smartphone and stored there for 14 days.\n\nFor exposure logging, the app downloads a list, which is updated daily, of the random IDs of all users who have shared their random IDs via their official coronavirus app. This list is then compared with the random IDs of other users which have been recorded by your smartphone.\n\nThe app will inform you if it detects a possible exposure. In this case, the app gains access to the data recorded by your smartphone about the possible exposure (date, duration and Bluetooth signal strength of the contact). The Bluetooth signal strength is used to derive the physical distance to the other user (the stronger the signal, the smaller the distance). The app analyses this information in order to calculate your risk of infection and to give you recommendations for what to do next. This analysis is only performed locally on your smartphone.\n\nApart from you, nobody (not even the RKI or the health authorities of participating countries) will know whether a possible exposure has been detected and what risk of infection has been identified for you.\n\nThe app’s privacy notice (including information about the data processing carried out for the transnational exposure logging feature) can be found in the menu under „App Information“ > „Data Privacy“."</string>
    <!-- XHED: Header of the delta onboarding screen for interoperability. If the user opens the app for the first time after the interoperability update -->
    <string name="interoperability_onboarding_delta_title" translatable="false">Transnational exposure logging</string>
    <!-- XTXT: Description of the interoperability extension of the app. Below interoperability_onboarding_delta_title -->
    <string name="interoperability_onboarding_delta_subtitle" translatable="false">The functionality of the Corona-Warn-App has been extended. Several countries are now working together to enable transnational alerts via a joint exchange server. For example, contacts with users of an official coronavirus app from other participating countries can now also be taken into account during exposure logging.</string>
    <!-- YMSG: Onboarding tracing step third section in interoperability after the title. -->
    <string name="interoperability_onboarding_delta_randomid" translatable="false">To do this, the app downloads a list, which is updated daily, of the random IDs of all users who have shared their random IDs via their own app. This list is then compared with the random IDs recorded by your smartphone.</string>
    <!-- YMSG: Onboarding tracing step third section in interoperability after the title. -->
    <string name="interoperability_onboarding_delta_free_download" translatable="false">The daily download of the list with the random IDs is usually free of charge for you. Specifically, this means that mobile network operators do not charge you for the data used by the app in this context, and nor do they apply roaming charges for this in other EU countries. Please contact your mobile network operator for more information.</string>
    <!-- XHED: Title for the privacy card-->
    <string name="submission_positive_other_warning_privacy_title" translatable="false">"Declaration of consent"</string>
    <!-- YTXT: Body text for the privacy card-->
    <string name="submission_positive_other_warning_privacy_body" translatable="false">"<b>By tapping on „Accept“, you consent to your random IDs from the last 14 days, along with any optional information you provide about the onset of your symptoms, being transmitted to the app’s server system.</b> This information will be used to assess the risk of infection for app users with whom you have come into contact, and to warn them if there is a risk that they are infected. In order to be able to warn the users of official coronavirus apps in other participating countries, the app’s server system will also make this information available to the joint exchange server operated by the participating countries.\n\nNeither other users nor the RKI or the health authorities of participating countries can infer your identity, name or other personal information from the data transmitted.\n\nTransmitting your random IDs and any information about the onset of your symptoms for transnational alerts is voluntary. You will not be penalised if you do not share this information. Since it is not possible to trace or check whether and how you use the app, nobody but you will know whether you provide your random IDs.\n\nYou can withdraw your consent at any time by deleting the app. This withdrawal of your consent will not affect the lawfulness of the processing carried out on the basis of the consent prior to the withdrawal.\n\nFurther information – including about the participating countries and their health authorities responsible for data protection matters – can be found in the menu under „App Information“ > „Data Privacy“."</string>
    <!-- XHED: onboarding(tracing) - headline for consent information -->
    <string name="onboarding_tracing_headline_consent" translatable="false">"Declaration of consent"</string>
    <!-- YTXT: onboarding(tracing) - body for consent information -->
    <string name="onboarding_tracing_body_consent" translatable="false">"You need to enable exposure logging to find out whether you have had possible exposures involving app users in the participating countries and are therefore at risk of infection yourself. By tapping on the “Activate exposure logging” button, you agree to enabling the exposure logging feature and to the associated data processing by the app.\n\nIn order to use the exposure logging feature, you will also have to enable the “COVID-19 Exposure Notifications” functionality provided by Google on your Android smartphone and grant the Corona-Warn-App permission to use this.\n\nWhen COVID-19 Exposure Notifications are enabled, your Android smartphone continuously generates random IDs and sends them via Bluetooth so that they can be received by other smartphones near you. Your Android smartphone, in turn, receives the random IDs of other smartphones. Your own random IDs and those received from other smartphones are recorded by your Android smartphone and stored there for 14 days.\n\nFor exposure logging, the app downloads a list, which is updated daily, of the random IDs of all users who have shared their random IDs via their official coronavirus app. This list is then compared with the random IDs of other users which have been recorded by your smartphone.\n\nThe app will inform you if it detects a possible exposure. In this case, the app gains access to the data recorded by your smartphone about the possible exposure (date, duration and Bluetooth signal strength of the contact). The Bluetooth signal strength is used to derive the physical distance to the other user (the stronger the signal, the smaller the distance). The app analyses this information in order to calculate your risk of infection and to give you recommendations for what to do next. This analysis is only performed locally on your smartphone.\n\nApart from you, nobody (not even the RKI or the health authorities of participating countries) will know whether a possible exposure has been detected and what risk of infection has been identified for you.\n\nTo withdraw your consent to the exposure logging feature, you can disable the feature by using the toggle switch in the app or delete the app. If you would like to use the exosure logging feature again, you can toggle the feature back on or reinstall the app. If you disable the exposure logging feature, the app will no longer check for possible exposures. If you also wish to stop your device sending and receiving random IDs, you will need to disable COVID-19 Exposure Notifications in your Android smartphone settings. Please note that your own random IDs and those received from other smartphones which are stored by your Android smartphone’s COVID-19 Exposure Notification functionality will not be deleted by the app. You can only permanently delete these in your Android smartphone settings.\n\nThe app’s privacy notice (including information about the data processing carried out for the transnational exposure logging feature) can be found in the menu under „App Information“ > „Data Privacy“."</string>
</resources>
