<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <!-- XHED: Header of private data in the delta onboarding interoperability view -->
    <string name="interoperability_onboarding_delta_footerTitle" translatable="false">"Information on Data Processing"</string>
    <!-- XTXT: Description of private data in the delta onboarding interoperability view. Below interoperability_onboarding_delta_footerTitle -->
    <string name="interoperability_onboarding_delta_footerDescription" translatable="false">"You do not need to change anything to find out whether you have had possible exposures involving app users in the participating countries and are therefore at risk of infection yourself. You just need to make sure that the exposure logging feature is still enabled. Exposure logging will automatically warn you about any possible exposure involving another user of the Corona-Warn-App or any other official coronavirus app.\n\nIf you have enabled the “COVID-19 Exposure Notifications” functionality on your smartphone, then your Android smartphone continuously generates random IDs and sends them via Bluetooth so that they can be received by other smartphones near you. Your Android smartphone, in turn, receives the random IDs of other smartphones. Your own random IDs and those received from other smartphones are recorded by your Android smartphone and stored there for 14 days.\n\nFor exposure logging, the app downloads up-to-date lists every day of the random IDs of all users who have shared their test result (more precisely: their own random IDs) via their official coronavirus app in order to warn other users. These lists are then compared with the random IDs of other users which have been recorded by your Android smartphone.\n\nThe app will inform you if it detects a possible exposure. In this case, the app gains access to the data recorded by your Android smartphone about the possible exposure (date, duration and Bluetooth signal strength of the contact). The Bluetooth signal strength is used to derive the physical distance to the other user (the stronger the signal, the smaller the distance). The app analyses this information in order to calculate your risk of infection and to give you recommendations for what to do next. This analysis is only performed locally on your Android smartphone.\n\nApart from you, nobody (not even the RKI or the health authorities of participating countries) will know whether a possible exposure has been detected and what risk of infection has been identified for you.\n\nThe app’s privacy notice (including information about the data processing carried out for the transnational exposure logging feature) can be found in the menu under „App Information“ > „Data Privacy“."</string>
    <!-- XHED: onboarding(tracing) - headline for consent information -->
    <string name="onboarding_tracing_headline_consent" translatable="false">"Consent"</string>
    <!-- YTXT: onboarding(tracing) - body for consent information -->
    <string name="onboarding_tracing_body_consent" translatable="false">"You need to enable exposure logging to find out whether you have had possible exposures involving app users in the participating countries and are therefore at risk of infection yourself. By tapping on the “Activate exposure logging” button, you agree to enabling the exposure logging feature and to the associated data processing by the app.\n\nIn order to use the exposure logging feature, you will also have to enable the “COVID-19 Exposure Notifications” functionality provided by Google on your Android smartphone and grant the Corona-Warn-App permission to use this.\n\nYour Android smartphone will then continuously generate random IDs and send them via Bluetooth so that they can be received by other smartphones near you. Your Android smartphone, in turn, receives the random IDs of other smartphones. Your own random IDs and those received from other smartphones are recorded by your Android smartphone and stored there for 14 days.\n\nFor exposure logging, the app downloads up-to-date lists every day of the random IDs of all users who have shared their test result (more precisely: their own random IDs) via their official coronavirus app in order to warn other users. These lists are then compared with the random IDs of other users which have been recorded by your Android smartphone.\n\nThe app will inform you if it detects a possible exposure. In this case, the app gains access to the data recorded by your Android smartphone about the possible exposure (date, duration and Bluetooth signal strength of the contact). The Bluetooth signal strength is used to derive the physical distance to the other user (the stronger the signal, the smaller the distance). The app analyses this information in order to calculate your risk of infection and to give you recommendations for what to do next. This analysis is only performed locally on your Android smartphone.\n\nApart from you, nobody (not even the RKI or the health authorities of participating countries) will know whether a possible exposure has been detected and what risk of infection has been identified for you.\n\nYou can withdraw your consent to the exposure logging feature at any time by either disabling the feature using the toggle switch in the app or deleting the app. If you would like to use the exposure logging feature again, you can toggle the feature back on or reinstall the app. If you disable the exposure logging feature, the app will no longer check for possible exposures. If you also wish to stop your device sending and receiving random IDs, you will need to disable the “COVID-19 Exposure Notifications” functionality in your Android smartphone’s settings. Please note that the app will not delete your random IDs or those received from other smartphones which have been recorded by this functionality on your Android smartphone. You can only permanently delete these in your Android smartphone settings.\n\nThe app’s privacy notice (including information about the data processing carried out for the transnational exposure logging feature) can be found in the menu under „App Information“ > „Data Privacy“."</string>
    <!-- XHED: Page subheadline for consent sub section your consent  -->
    <string name="submission_consent_your_consent_subsection_headline" translatable="false">"Your Consent"</string>
    <!-- YTXT: Body for consent sub section your consent subtext -->
    <string name="submission_consent_your_consent_subsection_tapping_agree" translatable="false">"By tapping on “Accept”, you consent to the following steps:"</string>
    <!-- YTXT: Body for consent sub section your consent subtext first point  -->
    <string name="submission_consent_your_consent_subsection_first_point" translatable="false">"<b>"The app will retrieve your test result.</b> If you change your mind later, you can delete the test in the app."</string>
    <!-- YTXT: Body for consent sub section your consent subtext second point  -->
    <string name="submission_consent_your_consent_subsection_second_point" translatable="false">"<b>If you have tested positive for coronavirus, the app will share your test result in order to warn other users whom you have encountered. This applies to users of coronavirus apps from the above countries and users who were simultaneously checked in at the same event or place as you. In the case of rapid tests, only users of the Corona-Warn-App will be warned.</b>"</string>
    <!-- YTXT: Body for consent sub section your consent subtext third point  -->
    <string name="submission_consent_your_consent_subsection_third_point" translatable="false">"<b>"If you provide additional information about the onset of your symptoms, this will also be shared."</b>"</string>
    <!-- YTXT: Body for consent sub section your consent subtext fourth point  -->
    <string name="submission_consent_your_consent_subsection_fourth_point" translatable="false">"You can withdraw your consent at any time. The setting for this can be found under "Display Test". Before sharing your test result, you will be reminded of your consent."</string>
    <!-- YTXT: Body for your consent screen agreement share test results -->
    <string name="submission_your_consent_agreement_share_test_results" translatable="false">"<b>"If you have tested positive for coronavirus, the app will share your test result in order to warn other users whom you have encountered.</b>\n\n<b>This warning only affects users who were simultaneously checked in at the same event or place as you and users of coronavirus apps in the following countries:</b>"</string>
    <!-- YTXT: Body for your consent screen agreement share symptoms -->
    <string name="submission_your_consent_agreement_share_symptoms" translatable="false">"<b>In the case of rapid tests, only users of the Corona-Warn-App will be warned. If you provide additional information about the onset of symptoms, this will be also shared.</b>\n\nYou can withdraw your consent by disabling “Warn Others” above."</string>
    <!-- YTXT: Body for your consent screen agreement share symptoms with additional hint for test result-->
    <string name="submission_your_consent_agreement_share_symptoms_2" translatable="false"><b>In the case of rapid tests, only users of the Corona-Warn-App will be warned. If you provide additional information about the onset of symptoms, this will be also shared.</b>\n\nYou can withdraw your consent by disabling “Warn others” above. Your test result will then be shown to you.</string>
    <!-- YTXT: Body for keys submission no consent text first part-->
    <string name="submission_no_consent_your_consent_subsection_body_first_part" translatable="false">"By tapping on “Accept”, you consent to the following:"</string>
    <!-- YTXT: Body for keys submission no consent text second part-->
    <string name="submission_no_consent_your_consent_subsection_body_second_part" translatable="false">"<b>The app will share your test result in order to warn users whom you have encountered. This applies to users of coronavirus apps from the above countries and users who were simultaneously checked in at the same event or place as you. In the case of rapid tests, only users of the Corona-Warn-App will be warned. If you provide additional information about the onset of symptoms, this will be also shared.</b>"</string>
    <!-- YTXT: Body for keys submission no consent text third part-->
    <string name="submission_no_consent_your_consent_subsection_body_third_part" translatable="false">"In the next step, grant your consent to access random IDs."</string>
    <!-- YTXT: Body for keys submission no consent text fourth part-->
    <string name="submission_no_consent_your_consent_subsection_body_fourth_part" translatable="false">"If you have already warned other users, you can withdraw your consent by deleting the app."</string>

    <!-- XTXT: Title for legal information of the contact diary onboarding screen -->
    <string name="contact_diary_onboarding_privacy_information_title" translatable="false">"Information on Data Processing"</string>
    <!-- XTXT: Title for the contact diary onboarding privacy information first section -->
    <string name="contact_diary_onboarding_privacy_information_first_section_title" translatable="false">"You will retain full control over all of the information you record"</string>
    <!-- XTXT: Body for the contact diary onboarding privacy information first section -->
    <string name="contact_diary_onboarding_privacy_information_first_section_body_one" translatable="false">Using this additional feature of the Corona-Warn-App is voluntary. Only you decide which people and places you record.</string>
    <!-- XTXT: Body for the contact diary onboarding privacy information first section -->
    <string name="contact_diary_onboarding_privacy_information_first_section_body_two" translatable="false">"Neither the RKI nor any other agency has access to the information you enter in the contact journal. The information is only stored in encrypted form on your Android smartphone."</string>
    <!-- XTXT: Title for the contact diary onboarding privacy information second section title -->
    <string name="contact_diary_onboarding_privacy_information_second_section_title" translatable="false">"Please respect other people’s privacy"</string>
    <!-- XTXT: Body for the contact diary onboarding privacy information second section -->
    <string name="contact_diary_onboarding_privacy_information_second_section_body_one" translatable="false">"Please think carefully about with whom you share the information recorded in your contact journal, and how you share it. The information is meant to help you remember – it is not intended for anyone else. If the public health office (Gesundheitsamt) asks for your help with contact tracing, then sharing your entries is appropriate."</string>
    <!-- XTXT: Body for the contact diary onboarding privacy information second section -->
    <string name="contact_diary_onboarding_privacy_information_second_section_body_two" translatable="false">"Private individuals as well as companies are not allowed to make you disclose the information you have recorded. Please respect the wishes of anyone who does not want to be recorded in your contact journal."</string>

    <!-- XHED: Title for the consent displayed above the button in the survey consent screen -->
    <string name="datadonation_details_survey_consent_info_card_title" translatable="false">"Your Consent"</string>
    <!-- XTXT: Text for the consent body displayed above the button in the survey consent screen -->
    <string name="datadonation_details_survey_consent_info_card_body" translatable="false">"By tapping on “Accept”, you consent to the following:\n\nBefore your participation link can be shown to you, the authenticity of your app is checked once. For this purpose, a unique identifier is generated by your smartphone and transmitted to Google in the U.S. or other third countries, so that Google can confirm the authenticity of your app to the RKI. The identifier contains information about the version of your smartphone and the app. On this basis, Google may be able to infer your identity and learn that your smartphone has been authenticated. Google does not receive any other information from the app during this process. This ensures that each user can only participate in the survey once, so as not to distort the statistics."</string>
    <!-- XTXT: First bullet point in the consent body displayed above the button in the survey consent screen -->
    <string name="datadonation_details_survey_consent_bullet_point_one" translatable="false">"Your consent is voluntary. If you do not give your consent for the purposes of the survey, you will still be able to use the whole app."</string>
    <!-- XTXT: Second bullet point in the consent body displayed above the button in the survey consent screen -->
    <string name="datadonation_details_survey_consent_bullet_point_two" translatable="false">"Even after you have given your consent, you do not have to participate in the survey. You can stop the survey at any time."</string>
    <!-- XTXT: Third bullet point in the consent body displayed above the button in the survey consent screen -->
    <string name="datadonation_details_survey_consent_bullet_point_three" translatable="false">"You need to be at least 16 years old to give your consent."</string>
    <!-- YTXT: Text on the bottom of the survey consent screen that opens a new screen about more information-->
    <string name="datadonation_details_survey_consent_bottom_link" translatable="false">"Detailed information about this data processing and your consent."</string>
    <!-- XHED: Title for the information box in the survey consent detail screen -->
    <string name="datadonation_survey_consent_details_title" translatable="false">"Verification of Authenticity and Transfer to a Third Country"</string>
    <!-- XTXT: Text for the information box in the survey consent detail screen -->
    <string name="datadonation_survey_consent_details_text" translatable="false">"To confirm the authenticity of your app, your smartphone will generate a unique identifier that contains information about the version of your smartphone and the app. This is necessary to prevent users from participating in the survey more than once, as this could distort the results of the survey. Once generated, the identifier will be transmitted once to Google. This may result in data being transferred to the U.S. or other third countries. There, the level of data protection may not be considered equivalent under European law and it may not be possible to enforce your European data protection rights. In particular, there is a possibility that once the transmitted data reaches Google, it may be accessed and analyzed by security authorities in the third country, even if they have no specific grounds for suspicion, for example by linking the data with other information. This only concerns the identifier sent to Google. Google will not receive the other information about your participation in the survey. It may however be possible for Google to infer your identity from the identifier and learn that your smartphone has been authenticated. "</string>

    <!-- XTXT: onboarding privacy preserving analytics (ppa) - consent title -->
    <string name="ppa_onboarding_consent_title" translatable="false">"Your Consent"</string>
    <!-- XTXT: Body for Privacy-preserving Analytics onboarding -->
    <string name="ppa_onboarding_privacy_information_body" translatable="false">"By tapping on “Accept”, you consent to the following:\n\nThe app will transmit information it records to the RKI, on a daily basis. The data concerns possible exposures and warnings that have been displayed to you, test results you have retrieved, and whether you have warned other users, and information about your smartphone’s operating system. If you have provided further details above (region, age group), then the RKI will also receive this information.\n\nThe RKI will compile this data into statistics and analyze it to assess the effectiveness and functioning of the app, and draw conclusions regarding the pandemic. The resulting knowledge will help to improve the app’s features and make it more user-friendly, as well as to inform other pandemic response measures.\n\nBefore your data is analyzed, it is necessary to ensure that each app that shares data is only counted once, so as not to distort the statistics. This is why the authenticity of your app needs to be verified. For this purpose, a unique identifier is generated by your smartphone and transmitted to Google in the U.S. or other third countries, so that Google can confirm the authenticity of your app to the RKI. The identifier contains information about the version of your smartphone and the app. On this basis, Google may be able to infer your identity and learn that your smartphone has been authenticated. Google does not receive any other information from the app during this process.\n\nYou can withdraw your consent at any time by disabling the data sharing feature in the app's settings."</string>
    <!-- XTXT: Body point consent for Privacy-preserving Analytics -->
    <string name="ppa_onboarding_privacy_information_point_consent" translatable="false">"Your consent is voluntary. If you do not give your consent, you will still be able to use the app."</string>
    <!-- XTXT: Body point identity for Privacy-preserving Analytics -->
    <string name="ppa_onboarding_privacy_information_point_identity" translatable="false">"If you share data about your use of the app, your identity will still be kept secret from the RKI. This means the RKI will not find out who you are or who you have met. No profiles will be created either."</string>
    <!-- XTXT: Body point sixteen for Privacy-preserving Analytics -->
    <string name="ppa_onboarding_privacy_information_point_sixteen" translatable="false">"You need to be at least 16 years old to give your consent."</string>
    <!-- XHED: Title for Privacy-preserving Analytics additional info  -->
    <string name="ppa_onboarding_more_info_title" translatable="false">"Verification of authenticity and transfer to a third country"</string>
    <!-- XTXT: Body for Privacy-preserving Analytics additional info -->
    <string name="ppa_onboarding_more_info_body" translatable="false">"To confirm the authenticity of your app, your smartphone will generate a unique identifier that contains information about the version of your smartphone and the app. This is necessary to prevent data from being transmitted to the RKI more than once or in an unauthorised manner, as this could distort the results of the analysis. The identifier will be transmitted to Google. This may result in data being transferred to the U.S. or other third countries. There, the level of data protection may not be considered equivalent under European law and it may not be possible to enforce your European data protection rights. In particular, there is a possibility that once the transmitted data reaches Google, it may be accessed and analyzed by security authorities in the third country, even if they have no specific grounds for suspicion, for example by linking the data with other information. This only concerns the identifier sent to Google. Google will not receive the other information about how you use the Corona-Warn-App. It may however be possible for Google to infer your identity from the identifier and learn that your smartphone has been authenticated.\n\nIf you do not consent to this transfer of your data to a third country, please do not tap on “Accept”. You will still be able to use the app, but not the data sharing feature."</string>
    <!-- XTXT: onboarding privacy preserving analytics (ppa) - consent title -->
    <string name="ppa_onboarding_privacy_information_title" translatable="false">"Your Consent"</string>
    <!-- XTXT: Body for Privacy-preserving Analytics settings -->
    <string name="ppa_settings_privacy_information_body" translatable="false">"By enabling “Share Data” above, you consent to the following:\n\nThe app will transmit information it records to the RKI, on a daily basis. The data concerns possible exposures and warnings that have been displayed to you, test results you have retrieved, and whether you have warned other users, and information about your smartphone’s operating system. If you have provided further details above (region, age group), then the RKI will also receive this information.\n\nThe RKI will compile this data into statistics and analyze it to assess the effectiveness and functioning of the app, and draw conclusions regarding the pandemic. The resulting knowledge will help to improve the app’s features and make it more user-friendly, as well as to inform other pandemic response measures.\n\nBefore your data is analyzed, it is necessary to ensure that each app that shares data is only counted once, so as not to distort the statistics. This is why the authenticity of your app needs to be verified. For this purpose, a unique identifier is generated by your smartphone and transmitted to Google in the U.S. or other third countries, so that Google can confirm the authenticity of your app to the RKI. The identifier contains information about the version of your smartphone and the app. On this basis, Google may be able to infer your identity and learn that your smartphone has been authenticated. Google does not receive any other information from the app during this process.\n\n You can withdraw your consent at any time by disabling “Share Data” above."</string>

    <!-- XHED: Title for debug upload screen privacy card -->
    <string name="debugging_debuglog_privacy_card_title" translatable="false">"Data protection and data security"</string>
    <!-- YTXT: First bullet point for debug upload screen privacy card -->
    <string name="debug_log_privacy_card_section_body_one" translatable="false">"Recording the error report is voluntary."</string>
    <!-- YTXT: Second bullet point for debug upload screen privacy card -->
    <string name="debug_log_privacy_card_container_section_two" translatable="false">"Initially, only you will have access to the error report. You can then decide whether to send the error report to the technical support team, whether to save the error report on your smartphone first, or whether to stop and erase the recorded information. If you first save the error report locally, this will give you the opportunity to view the error report yourself before submitting it to support."</string>
    <!-- YTXT: Third bullet point for debug upload screen privacy card -->
    <string name="debug_log_privacy_card_container_section_three" translatable="false">"The error report contains sensitive information, such as details of your test result or the infection risk determined for you. It does not contain any information about the QR codes you used when registering your test, any information you recorded in the contact journal, or any information about your identity."</string>
    <!-- YTXT: Fourth bullet point for debug upload screen privacy card -->
    <string name="debug_log_privacy_card_container_section_four" translatable="false">"We do not recommend publishing the error reports or sending them by email."</string>
    <!-- YTXT: Fifth bullet point for debug upload screen privacy card -->
    <string name="debug_log_privacy_card_container_section_five" translatable="false">"Private individuals as well as companies are not allowed to make you share a recorded error report with them."</string>

    <!-- XHED: Title for Bugreporting share log Privacy Card -->
    <string name="debugging_debuglog_share_privacy_card_title" translatable="false">"Your consent"</string>
    <!-- YTXT: First body section for Bugreporting share log Privacy Card -->
    <string name="debugging_debuglog_share_privacy_card_body_1" translatable="false">"By tapping on “Agree and Send”, you consent to the following steps:"</string>
    <!-- YTXT: First bullet point for Bugreporting share log Privacy Card -->
    <string name="debugging_debuglog_share_privacy_card_bullet_point_1" translatable="false">"The error report you create will be sent to the RKI for error analysis purposes. The RKI will analyse the error report in order to be able to identify and fix possible causes of the errors that occur in your app. If you provide the error report ID to the technical support team, then the RKI will be able to associate the error report with you personally."</string>
    <!-- YTXT: Second bullet point for Bugreporting share log Privacy Card -->
    <string name="debugging_debuglog_share_privacy_card_bullet_point_2" translatable="false">"Before the report is sent to the RKI, the authenticity of your app is checked once. For this purpose, a unique identifier is generated by your smartphone and transmitted to Google in the US or other third countries, so that Google can confirm the authenticity of your app to the RKI. The identifier contains information about the version of your smartphone and the app. Google may thus be able to infer your identity and learn that your smartphone has been authenticated. Google will not receive any further information from the app or the error report during this process."</string>
    <!-- YTXT: Second body section for Bugreporting share log Privacy Card -->
    <string name="debugging_debuglog_share_privacy_card_body_2" translatable="false">"If, after sending the report, you have provided your error report ID to the technical support team, then you may also request at any time that the other information you provided, the error report ID, and the error report itself be erased. Otherwise, the error report will be automatically erased after 14 days."</string>

    <!-- Trace Location QR Info Privacy Strings -->
    <!-- XHED: Title for privacy card -->
    <string name="trace_location_privacy_card_title_text" translatable="false">"Data protection and data security"</string>
    <!-- XTXT: Subtitle for privacy card -->
    <string name="trace_location_privacy_card_subtitle_text" translatable="false">"If you tap on “Next”, you can create a QR code for your guests."</string>
    <!-- XTXT: First bulletpoint title for privacy card -->
    <string name="trace_location_privacy_card_first_bulletpoint_title_text" translatable="false">"Your event or place details will be stored in encoded form in a printable QR code."</string>
    <!-- XTXT: First bulletpoint subtitle for privacy card -->
    <string name="trace_location_privacy_card_fist_bulletpoint_subtitle_text" translatable="false">"Your guests can then scan the QR code with the app."</string>
    <!-- XTXT: Second bulleptoint title for privacy card -->
    <string name="trace_location_privacy_card_second_bulletpoint_title_text" translatable="false">"Please ensure that you are as specific as possible about the name, category and time of your event or place, and the typical length of stay."</string>
    <!-- XTXT: Second vulletpoint subtitle for privacy card -->
    <string name="trace_location_pricacy_card_second_bulletpoint_subtitle_text" translatable="false">"The more accurate your information, the more reliably your guests can be warned."</string>
    <!-- XTXT: Third bulletpoint text for privacy card -->
    <string name="trace_location_privacy_card_third_bulletpoint_text" translatable="false">"Please display the QR code in such a way that all your guests can scan it while observing the social distancing and hygiene rules (at least 1.5 meters)."</string>
    <!-- XTXT: Fourth bulletpoint text for privacy card -->
    <string name="trace_location_privacy_card_fourth_bulletpoint_text" translatable="false">"We recommend creating new QR codes for places at regular intervals, so that warnings are as reliable as possible over time and in order to prevent the QR codes from being misused."</string>

    <!-- Trace Location Onboarding Strings -->
    <!-- XHED: Title for the trace location onboarding consent card -->
    <string name="trace_location_onboarding_card_title" translatable="false">Your consent</string>
    <!-- YMSG: Onboarding trace location bullet points introduction -->
    <string name="trace_location_onboarding_body_intro" translatable="false">By tapping on “Accept”, you consent to the following steps:</string>
    <!-- YMSG: Onboarding trace location bullet points -->
    <string name="trace_location_onboarding_body_consent2" translatable="false">The app will remember which events or places you’ve checked in at for 16 days.</string>
    <!-- YMSG: Onboarding trace location bullet points -->
    <string name="trace_location_onboarding_body_consent3" translatable="false">If you scan a QR code to check in somewhere, this will create a record for the event or place on your smartphone.</string>
    <!-- YMSG: Onboarding trace location bullet points -->
    <string name="trace_location_onboarding_body_consent4" translatable="false">If a user who was checked in at the same time as you later tests positive and uses the warning feature, you will automatically receive a warning based on the event ID – even if your smartphone didn’t receive any random IDs from the user who tested positive.</string>
    <!-- YMSG: Onboarding trace location bullet points -->
    <string name="trace_location_onboarding_body_consent5" translatable="false">If you later use the warning feature yourself, all of the other users who were checked in at the same time as you at an event or place listed under “My check-ins” will receive a warning based on the event ID.</string>
    <!-- YMSG: Onboarding trace location bullet points -->
    <string name="trace_location_onboarding_body_consent6" translatable="false">You can erase a check-in at any time under “My check-ins”. In this case, you will only be warned if your smartphone identifies a possible exposure after receiving the random IDs of the user who tested positive.</string>

    <!-- RAT Profile Onboarding -->
    <!-- XHED: Title for RAT Profile onboarding consent card -->
    <string name="rat_profile_onboarding_card_title" translatable="false">Data protection and data security</string>
    <!-- YMSG: RAT Profile Onboarding bullet points -->
    <string name="rat_profile_onboarding_card_consent1" translatable="false">Creating a rapid test profile in the app, and using it, are voluntary.</string>
    <!-- YMSG: RAT Profile Onboarding bullet points -->
    <string name="rat_profile_onboarding_card_consent2" translatable="false">The app converts the data you enter for your rapid test profile into your personal QR code. The QR code then contains all the data you entered.</string>
    <!-- YMSG: RAT Profile Onboarding bullet points -->
    <string name="rat_profile_onboarding_card_consent3" translatable="false">At a testing point, you can then have your rapid test profile’s QR code scanned as a means of quickly and securely providing your data to the testing point. The testing point will need your data to carry out the test. However, you do not need the app to provide your data. You decide yourself which data is included in the QR code, and which information you communicate to the testing point by other means.</string>
    <!-- YMSG: RAT Profile Onboarding bullet points -->
    <string name="rat_profile_onboarding_card_consent4" translatable="false">To begin with, only you will have access to your personal rapid test profile. Other people can only access the personal data contained in your rapid test profile if you show them your rapid test profile’s QR code. This will not provide access to other data from the app (e.g. your check-ins or information in your contact journal).</string>
    <!-- YMSG: RAT Profile Onboarding bullet points -->
    <string name="rat_profile_onboarding_card_consent5" translatable="false">You have the possibility to delete your rapid test profile at any time. Until then, it will remain stored in the app on your smartphone.</string>
    <!-- YMSG: RAT Profile Onboarding bullet points -->
    <string name="rat_profile_onboarding_card_consent6" translatable="false">The QR code contains your personal information. Do not provide your personal QR code to anyone if you do not want the data to be read. We do not recommend publishing your personal QR code or sending it by email.</string>
    <!-- YMSG: RAT Profile Onboarding bullet points -->
    <string name="rat_profile_onboarding_card_consent7" translatable="false">Private individuals as well as companies are not allowed to make you share your rapid test profile with them.</string>

    <!-- Vaccination Consent Privacy Strings  -->
    <!-- XHED: Title for privacy card -->
    <string name="vaccination_privacy_card_title_text" translatable="false">"Data protection and data security"</string>
    <!-- XTXT: First bulletpoint title for privacy card -->
    <string name="vaccination_privacy_card_first_bulletpoint_title_text" translatable="false">"Using the digital COVID Certificates is voluntary. There are other ways to prove that you are fully vaccinated, have a negative test result, or have recovered from a coronavirus infection."</string>
    <!-- XTXT: First bulletpoint title for privacy card -->
    <string name="vaccination_privacy_card_second_bulletpoint_title_text" translatable="false">"The COVID Certificates contain personal data (involving vaccinations, test results or a previous infection). In cases where you are required by law to show proof, it is sufficient to show the QR code of the certificate in the app. Please note that you may be required to present an identification document during the check. Do not provide certificates and the QR codes to anyone if you do not want the data to be read."</string>
    <!-- XTXT: First bulletpoint title for privacy card -->
    <string name="vaccination_privacy_card_third_bulletpoint_title_text" translatable="false">"When you present the QR code of a certificate in the app for verification, others will be able to find out whether you have tested negative, are fully vaccinated, or have proof that you have recovered from a coronavirus infection. During verification, the official verification app will also display the name and date of birth. In the case of test certificates, the date of sampling will also be displayed."</string>
    <!-- XTXT: First bulletpoint title for privacy card -->
    <string name="vaccination_privacy_card_fourth_bulletpoint_title_text" translatable="false">"You have the possibility to delete COVID-19 certificates in the app at any time. Until then, the certificates will be stored on your smartphone."</string>

    <!--    Green Certificate -->
    <!-- XTXT: Request GC title for privacy card -->
    <string name="request_green_certificate_privacy_title" translatable="false">Data protection and data security</string>
    <!-- XTXT: Request GC bullet point 1 for privacy card -->
    <string name="request_green_certificate_privacy_section_1" translatable="false">Requesting and using a digital COVID-19 test certificate is voluntary. There are other ways to prove that you have a negative test result.</string>
    <!-- XTXT: Request GC bullet point 2 for privacy card -->
    <string name="request_green_certificate_privacy_section_2" translatable="false">To create your test certificate, data is transmitted once in encrypted form to the RKI. The RKI signs this data electronically to confirm its validity. The RKI will not store the data.</string>
    <!-- XTXT: Request GC extra bullet point PCR test  for privacy card -->
    <string name="request_green_certificate_privacy_pcr_extra_section" translatable="false">To ensure that no one with your QR code can retrieve your test result, it is protected with your date of birth. Your date of birth is transmitted in encrypted form to the laboratory in order to retrieve the test result.</string>
    <!-- XTXT: Request GC bullet point 3 for privacy card -->
    <string name="request_green_certificate_privacy_section_3" translatable="false">The COVID-19 test certificate contains the data about your coronavirus test. In cases where you are required by law to prove a negative test result, it is sufficient to show the QR code in the app. Do not provide the test certificate to anyone if you do not want the data to be read.</string>
    <!-- XTXT: Request GC bullet point 4 for privacy card -->
    <string name="request_green_certificate_privacy_section_4" translatable="false">If you present the QR code of the test certificate in the app and it is scanned using the verification app, others will be able to find out your test result. During verification, the official verification app will also display your name and date of birth.</string>
    <!-- XTXT: Request GC bullet point 5 for privacy card -->
    <string name="request_green_certificate_privacy_section_5" translatable="false">You have the possibility to delete test certificates in the app at any time. Until then, the test certificates will be stored on your smartphone.</string>

    <!-- DCC Ticketing Sonsent Screen -->
    <!-- XTXT: DCC Ticketing: Consent One: Legal: Title -->
    <string name="dcc_ticketing_consent_one_legal_title" translatable="false">"Your consent"</string>
    <!-- XTXT: DCC Ticketing: Consent One: Legal: Body -->
    <string name="dcc_ticketing_consent_one_legal_body" translatable="false">"By tapping on “Accept”, you consent to the following steps:"</string>
    <!-- XTXT: DCC Ticketing: Consent One: Legal: Point 1 -->
    <string name="dcc_ticketing_consent_one_legal_point_1" translatable="false">"The app will retrieve from the provider the name and date of birth of the person specified at the time of booking, the booking details relevant to the verification (e.g. destination country and date of travel) and the certificate requirements specified by the provider for your booking."</string>
    <!-- XTXT: DCC Ticketing: Consent One: Legal: Point 2 -->
    <string name="dcc_ticketing_consent_one_legal_point_2" translatable="false">"Once retrieved, the app will use this data to determine which of your stored certificates can be used."</string>

    <!-- DCC Ticketing Consent Two Screen -->
    <!-- XTXT: DCC Ticketing: Consent Two: Legal: Title -->
    <string name="dcc_ticketing_consent_two_legal_title" translatable="false">"Your consent"</string>
    <!-- XTXT: DCC Ticketing: Consent Two: Legal: Body -->
    <string name="dcc_ticketing_consent_two_legal_body" translatable="false">"By tapping on “Accept”, you consent to the transfer of the following data to the verification partner:"</string>
    <!-- XTXT: DCC Ticketing: Consent Two: Legal: Point 1 -->
    <string name="dcc_ticketing_consent_two_legal_point_1" translatable="false">"Content and electronic signature of the selected certificate (including name and date of birth of the certificate holder, validity period, issuer and date of issue, vaccine/test/recovery details)."</string>
    <!-- XTXT: DCC Ticketing: Consent Two: Legal: Point 2 -->
    <string name="dcc_ticketing_consent_two_legal_point_2" translatable="false">"The booking details retrieved from the provider:"</string>
    <!-- XTXT: DCC Ticketing: Consent Two: Legal: Point 2-1 -->
    <string name="dcc_ticketing_consent_two_legal_point_2_1" translatable="false">"Period during which the certificate must be valid (travel duration or event date)"</string>
    <!-- XTXT: DCC Ticketing: Consent Two: Legal: Point 2-2 -->
    <string name="dcc_ticketing_consent_two_legal_point_2_2" translatable="false">"For travel bookings: Country of origin and country of destination or journey"</string>
    <!-- XTXT: DCC Ticketing: Consent Two: Legal: Point 2-3 -->
    <string name="dcc_ticketing_consent_two_legal_point_2_3" translatable="false">"For cross-border travel: Certificate requirements imposed by the destination country"</string>
    <!-- XTXT: DCC Ticketing: Consent Two: Legal: Point 2-4 -->
    <string name="dcc_ticketing_consent_two_legal_point_2_4" translatable="false">"Further certificate requirements on the part of the provider (e.g. which vaccines or test procedures are accepted)"</string>

    <!-- DCC Reissuance Consent Screen -->
    <!-- XTXT: DCC Reissuance legal header-->
    <string name="dcc_reissuance_legal_header" translatable="false">By tapping on “Accept”, you consent to the following steps:</string>
    <!-- XTXT: DCC Reissuance legal first bullet point-->
    <string name="dcc_reissuance_legal_one" translatable="false">The app will transmit the aforementioned certificates to the RKI for verification.</string>
    <!-- XTXT: DCC Reissuance legal second bullet point-->
    <string name="dcc_reissuance_legal_two" translatable="false">The RKI will check the certificates, issue renewed certificates and send these to your app.</string>

    <!-- Family Consent Screen -->
    <!-- XTXT: Family Consent Screen: Legal: Title -->
    <string name="family_consent_legal_title" translatable="false">"Your Consent"</string>
    <!-- XTXT: Family Consent Screen: Legal: Body -->
    <string name="family_consent_legal_body" translatable="false">"By tapping on “Accept”, you consent to the following step:"</string>
    <!-- XTXT: Family Consent Screen: Legal: Point 1 -->
    <string name="family_consent_legal_point_1" translatable="false">"<b>The app will retrieve the family member’s test result.</b>\nIf you change your mind later, you can delete the test in the app."</string>
    <!-- YTXT: Text on the bottom of the survey consent screen that opens a new screen about more information-->
    <string name="family_consent_legal_bottom_link" translatable="false">"Detailed information about this data processing and your consent."</string>

    <!-- SRS Submission Consent Screen -->
    <!-- XHED: Submission consent privacy card title -->
    <string name="srs_privacy_card_title_text" translatable="false">Your consent</string>
    <!-- XTXT: Submission consent privacy card subtitle -->
    <string name="srs_privacy_card_subtitle_text" translatable="false">By tapping on “Accept”, you consent to the following steps:</string>
    <!-- XTXT: Submission consent privacy card first bulletpoint -->
    <string name="srs_privacy_card_first_bulletpoint_text" translatable="false"><b>The app will share your positive test result in order to warn other Corona-Warn-App users whom you have encountered or who were simultaneously checked in at the same event or place as you.</b></string>
    <!-- XTXT: Submission consent privacy card second bulletpoint -->
    <string name="srs_privacy_card_second_bulletpoint_text" translatable="false">Before the test result can be shared, the <b>authenticity of your app is checked once</b>. For this purpose, a unique identifier is generated by your smartphone and transmitted to Google in the US or other third countries, so that Google can confirm the authenticity of your app to the RKI. The identifier contains information about the version of your smartphone and the app. Google may thus be able to infer your identity and learn that your smartphone has been authenticated. Google will not receive any further information from the app during this process.</string>
    <!-- XTXT: Submission consent privacy card third bulletpoint -->
    <string name="srs_privacy_card_third_bulletpoint_text" translatable="false"><b>If you provide additional information about the onset of your symptoms, this will also be shared.</b></string>

    <!-- SRS Submission Consent Detail Screen -->
    <!-- XHED: Title above the information box in the srs consent detail screen -->
    <string name="srs_details_survey_consent_details_title" translatable="false">"Detailed information on authentication and data protection risks in the US and other third countries"</string>
    <!-- XHED: Title for the information box in the srs consent detail screen -->
    <string name="srs_survey_consent_details_title" translatable="false">"Verification of authenticity and transfer to a third country"</string>
    <!-- XTXT: Text for the information box in the srs consent detail screen -->
    <string name="srs_survey_consent_details_text" translatable="false">"To confirm the authenticity of your app, your smartphone will generate a unique identifier that contains information about the version of your smartphone and the app. This is necessary to ensure that only users who actually use the Corona-Warn-App activate the warning feature after a positive self-test or with a test result that is not in the app, and to prevent manipulated warnings. The procedure also serves to ensure that users can only activate the warning feature after a positive self-test, or with a test result that is not available in the app, every three months.\n\nThe unique identifier generated during authentication will be transmitted once to Google when the warning feature is activated. This may result in data being transferred to the US or other third countries. There, the level of data protection may not be considered equivalent under European law and it may not be possible to enforce your European data protection rights. In particular, there is a possibility that once the transmitted data reaches Google, it may be accessed and analysed by security authorities in the third country, even if they have no specific grounds for suspicion, for example by linking the data with other information. This only concerns the identifier sent to Google. However, Google may be able to infer your identity from the identifier and learn that your smartphone has been authenticated for the purpose of warning others.\n\nIf you do not consent to this transfer of your data to a third country, please do not tap on “Accept”. You can still use the app, but it will not be possible to warn others after a positive self-test or with a test result that is not in the app."</string>
</resources>
