<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="interop_consent_body" translatable="false" />
    <!-- XHED: Header of private data in the delta onboarding interoperability view -->
    <string name="interoperability_onboarding_delta_footerTitle" translatable="false">"Information on Data Processing"</string>
    <!-- XTXT: Description of private data in the delta onboarding interoperability view. Below interoperability_onboarding_delta_footerTitle -->
    <string name="interoperability_onboarding_delta_footerDescription" translatable="false">"You do not need to change anything to find out whether you have had possible exposures involving app users in the participating countries and are therefore at risk of infection yourself. You just need to make sure that the exposure logging feature is still enabled. Exposure logging will automatically warn you about any possible exposure involving another user of the Corona-Warn-App or any other official coronavirus app.\n\nIf you have enabled the “COVID-19 Exposure Notifications” functionality on your smartphone, then your Android smartphone continuously generates random IDs and sends them via Bluetooth so that they can be received by other smartphones near you. Your Android smartphone, in turn, receives the random IDs of other smartphones. Your own random IDs and those received from other smartphones are recorded by your Android smartphone and stored there for 14 days.\n\nFor exposure logging, the app downloads up-to-date lists every day of the random IDs of all users who have shared their test result (more precisely: their own random IDs) via their official coronavirus app in order to warn other users. These lists are then compared with the random IDs of other users which have been recorded by your Android smartphone.\n\nThe app will inform you if it detects a possible exposure. In this case, the app gains access to the data recorded by your Android smartphone about the possible exposure (date, duration and Bluetooth signal strength of the contact). The Bluetooth signal strength is used to derive the physical distance to the other user (the stronger the signal, the smaller the distance). The app analyses this information in order to calculate your risk of infection and to give you recommendations for what to do next. This analysis is only performed locally on your Android smartphone.\n\nApart from you, nobody (not even the RKI or the health authorities of participating countries) will know whether a possible exposure has been detected and what risk of infection has been identified for you.\n\nThe app’s privacy notice (including information about the data processing carried out for the transnational exposure logging feature) can be found in the menu under „App Information“ > „Data Privacy“."</string>
    <!-- XHED: Title for the privacy card-->
    <string name="submission_positive_other_warning_privacy_title" translatable="false">"Declaration of Consent"</string>
    <!-- YTXT: Body text for the privacy card-->
    <string name="submission_positive_other_warning_privacy_body" translatable="false">"<b>By tapping on „Accept“, you consent to your random IDs from the last 14 days, along with any optional information you provide about the onset of your symptoms, being transmitted to the app’s server system.</b> This information will be used to assess the risk of infection for app users with whom you have come into contact, and to warn them if there is a risk that they are infected. In order to be able to warn the users of official coronavirus apps in other participating countries, the app’s server system will also make this information available to the joint exchange server operated by the participating countries.\n\nNeither other users nor the RKI or the health authorities of participating countries can infer your identity, name or other personal information from the data transmitted.\n\nTransmitting your random IDs and any information about the onset of your symptoms for transnational alerts is voluntary. You will not be penalised if you do not share this information. Since it is not possible to trace or check whether and how you use the app, nobody but you will know whether you provide your random IDs.\n\nYou can withdraw your consent at any time by deleting the app. This withdrawal of your consent will not affect the lawfulness of the processing carried out on the basis of the consent prior to the withdrawal.\n\nFurther information – including about the participating countries and their health authorities responsible for data protection matters – can be found in the menu under „App Information“ > „Data Privacy“."</string>
    <!-- XHED: onboarding(tracing) - headline for consent information -->
    <string name="onboarding_tracing_headline_consent" translatable="false">"Consent"</string>
    <!-- YTXT: onboarding(tracing) - body for consent information -->
    <string name="onboarding_tracing_body_consent" translatable="false">"You need to enable exposure logging to find out whether you have had possible exposures involving app users in the participating countries and are therefore at risk of infection yourself. By tapping on the “Activate exposure logging” button, you agree to enabling the exposure logging feature and to the associated data processing by the app.\n\nIn order to use the exposure logging feature, you will also have to enable the “COVID-19 Exposure Notifications” functionality provided by Google on your Android smartphone and grant the Corona-Warn-App permission to use this.\n\nYour Android smartphone will then continuously generate random IDs and send them via Bluetooth so that they can be received by other smartphones near you. Your Android smartphone, in turn, receives the random IDs of other smartphones. Your own random IDs and those received from other smartphones are recorded by your Android smartphone and stored there for 14 days.\n\nFor exposure logging, the app downloads up-to-date lists every day of the random IDs of all users who have shared their test result (more precisely: their own random IDs) via their official coronavirus app in order to warn other users. These lists are then compared with the random IDs of other users which have been recorded by your Android smartphone.\n\nThe app will inform you if it detects a possible exposure. In this case, the app gains access to the data recorded by your Android smartphone about the possible exposure (date, duration and Bluetooth signal strength of the contact). The Bluetooth signal strength is used to derive the physical distance to the other user (the stronger the signal, the smaller the distance). The app analyses this information in order to calculate your risk of infection and to give you recommendations for what to do next. This analysis is only performed locally on your Android smartphone.\n\nApart from you, nobody (not even the RKI or the health authorities of participating countries) will know whether a possible exposure has been detected and what risk of infection has been identified for you.\n\nYou can withdraw your consent to the exposure logging feature at any time by either disabling the feature using the toggle switch in the app or deleting the app. If you would like to use the exposure logging feature again, you can toggle the feature back on or reinstall the app. If you disable the exposure logging feature, the app will no longer check for possible exposures. If you also wish to stop your device sending and receiving random IDs, you will need to disable the “COVID-19 Exposure Notifications” functionality in your Android smartphone’s settings. Please note that the app will not delete your random IDs or those received from other smartphones which have been recorded by this functionality on your Android smartphone. You can only permanently delete these in your Android smartphone settings.\n\nThe app’s privacy notice (including information about the data processing carried out for the transnational exposure logging feature) can be found in the menu under „App Information“ > „Data Privacy“."</string>
    <!-- XHED: Page subheadline for consent sub section your consent  -->
   <string name="submission_consent_your_consent_subsection_headline" translatable="false">"Your Consent"</string>
    <!-- YTXT: Body for consent sub section your consent subtext -->
    <string name="submission_consent_your_consent_subsection_tapping_agree" translatable="false">"By tapping on “Accept”, you consent to the following steps:"</string>
    <!-- YTXT: Body for consent sub section your consent subtext first point  -->
    <string name="submission_consent_your_consent_subsection_first_point" translatable="false">"<b>The app will retrieve your test result.</b> If you change your mind later, you can delete the test in the app."</string>
    <!-- YTXT: Body for consent sub section your consent subtext second point  -->
    <string name="submission_consent_your_consent_subsection_second_point" translatable="false">"<b>If you have tested positive for coronavirus, the app will share your test result in order to warn other users whom you have encountered. This includes users of the official coronavirus apps of the countries mentioned above. If you provide additional information about the onset of your symptoms, this will also be shared.</b>"</string>
    <!-- YTXT: Body for consent sub section your consent subtext third point  -->
    <string name="submission_consent_your_consent_subsection_third_point" translatable="false">"You can withdraw your consent at any time. The setting for this can be found under “Display Test”. Before sharing your test result, you will be reminded of your consent and asked to confirm your willingness to share your test result."</string>
    <!-- YTXT: Body for your consent screen agreement share test results -->
    <string name="submission_your_consent_agreement_share_test_results" translatable="false">"<b>If you have tested positive for coronavirus, the app will share your test result in order to warn other users whom you have encountered.</b>\n\n<b>The warning will reach users of the official coronavirus apps of the following participating countries:</b>"</string>
    <!-- YTXT: Body for your consent screen agreement share symptoms -->
    <string name="submission_your_consent_agreement_share_symptoms" translatable="false">"<b>If you provide additional information about the onset of your symptoms, this will also be shared.</b>\n\nYou can withdraw your consent by disabling “Warn Others” above."</string>
    <!-- YTXT: Body for your consent screen agreement share symptoms with additional hint for test result-->
    <string name="submission_your_consent_agreement_share_symptoms_2" translatable="false"><b>If you provide additional information about the onset of your symptoms, this will also be shared.</b>\n\nYou can withdraw your consent by disabling “Warn others” above. Your test result will then be shown to you.</string>
    <!-- YTXT: Body for keys submission no consent text first part-->
    <string name="submission_no_consent_your_consent_subsection_body_first_part" translatable="false">"By tapping on “Accept”, you consent to the following:"</string>
    <!-- YTXT: Body for keys submission no consent text second part-->
    <string name="submission_no_consent_your_consent_subsection_body_second_part" translatable="false">"<b>The app will share your test result in order to warn other users of official coronavirus apps whom you have encountered. The warning will work in the countries mentioned above. If you provide additional information about the onset of your symptoms, this will also be shared.</b>In the next step, please share your test result (or more precisely: your random IDs from the last 14 days) by tapping on “Share”."</string>
    <!-- YTXT: Body for keys submission no consent text third part-->
    <string name="submission_no_consent_your_consent_subsection_body_third_part" translatable="false">"If you have already warned other users, you can withdraw your consent by deleting the app."</string>

    <!-- XTXT: Title for legal information of the contact diary onboarding screen -->
    <string name="contact_diary_onboarding_privacy_information_title" translatable="false">"Information on Data Processing"</string>
    <!-- XTXT: Title for the contact diary onboarding privacy information first section -->
    <string name="contact_diary_onboarding_privacy_information_first_section_title" translatable="false">"You will retain full control over all of the information you record"</string>
    <!-- XTXT: Body for the contact diary onboarding privacy information first section -->
    <string name="contact_diary_onboarding_privacy_information_first_section_body_one" translatable="false">Using this additional feature of the Corona-Warn-App is voluntary. Only you decide which people and places you record.</string>
    <!-- XTXT: Body for the contact diary onboarding privacy information first section -->
    <string name="contact_diary_onboarding_privacy_information_first_section_body_two" translatable="false">"Neither the RKI nor any other agency has access to the information you enter in the contact diary. The information is only stored in encrypted form on your Android smartphone."</string>
    <!-- XTXT: Title for the contact diary onboarding privacy information second section title -->
    <string name="contact_diary_onboarding_privacy_information_second_section_title" translatable="false">"Please respect other people’s privacy"</string>
    <!-- XTXT: Body for the contact diary onboarding privacy information second section -->
    <string name="contact_diary_onboarding_privacy_information_second_section_body_one" translatable="false">"Please think carefully about with whom you share the information recorded in your contact journal, and how you share it. The information is meant to help you remember – it is not intended for anyone else. If the public health office (Gesundheitsamt) asks for your help with contact tracing, then sharing your entries is appropriate."</string>
    <!-- XTXT: Body for the contact diary onboarding privacy information second section -->
    <string name="contact_diary_onboarding_privacy_information_second_section_body_two" translatable="false">"Private individuals as well as companies are not allowed to make you disclose the information you have recorded. Please respect the wishes of anyone who does not want to be recorded in your contact diary."</string>

    <!-- XHED: Title for the consent displayed above the button in the survey consent screen -->
    <string name="datadonation_details_survey_consent_info_card_title" translatable="false">"Your Consent"</string>
    <!-- XTXT: Text for the consent body displayed above the button in the survey consent screen -->
    <string name="datadonation_details_survey_consent_info_card_body" translatable="false">"By tapping on “Accept”, you consent to the following:\n\nBefore your participation link can be shown to you, the authenticity of your app is checked once. For this purpose, a unique identifier is generated by your smartphone and transmitted to Google in the U.S. or other third countries, so that Google can confirm the authenticity of your app to the RKI. The identifier contains information about the version of your smartphone and the app. On this basis, Apple [Google] may be able to infer your identity and learn that your smartphone has been authenticated. Google does not receive any other information from the app during this process. This ensures that each user can only participate in the survey once, so as not to distort the statistics."</string>
    <!-- XTXT: First bullet point in the consent body displayed above the button in the survey consent screen -->
    <string name="datadonation_details_survey_consent_bullet_point_one" translatable="false">"Your consent is voluntary. If you do not give your consent for the purposes of the survey, you will still be able to use the whole app."</string>
    <!-- XTXT: Second bullet point in the consent body displayed above the button in the survey consent screen -->
    <string name="datadonation_details_survey_consent_bullet_point_two" translatable="false">"Even after you have given your consent, you do not have to participate in the survey. You can stop the survey at any time."</string>
    <!-- XTXT: Third bullet point in the consent body displayed above the button in the survey consent screen -->
    <string name="datadonation_details_survey_consent_bullet_point_three" translatable="false">"You need to be at least 16 years old to give your consent."</string>
    <!-- YTXT: Text on the bottom of the survey consent screen that opens a new screen about more information-->
    <string name="datadonation_details_survey_consent_bottom_link" translatable="false">"Detailed information about this data processing and your consent."</string>
    <!-- XHED: Title for the information box in the survey consent detail screen -->
    <string name="datadonation_survey_consent_details_title" translatable="false">"Verification of Authenticity and Transfer to a Third Country"</string>
    <!-- XTXT: Text for the information box in the survey consent detail screen -->
    <string name="datadonation_survey_consent_details_text" translatable="false">"To confirm the authenticity of your app, your smartphone will generate a unique identifier that contains information about the version of your smartphone and the app. This is necessary to prevent users from participating in the survey more than once, as this could distort the results of the survey. Once generated, the identifier will be transmitted once to Google. This may result in data being transferred to the U.S. or other third countries. There, the level of data protection may not be considered equivalent under European law and it may not be possible to enforce your European data protection rights. In particular, there is a possibility that once the transmitted data reaches Google, it may be accessed and analyzed by security authorities in the third country, even if they have no specific grounds for suspicion, for example by linking the data with other information. This only concerns the identifier sent to Google. Google will not receive the other information about your participation in the survey. It may however be possible for Apple [Google] to infer your identity from the identifier and learn that your smartphone has been authenticated. "</string>

    <!-- XTXT: onboarding privacy preserving analytics (ppa) - consent title -->
    <string name="ppa_onboarding_consent_title" translatable="false">"Your Consent"</string>
    <!-- XTXT: Body for Privacy-preserving Analytics onboarding -->
 <string name="ppa_onboarding_privacy_information_body" translatable="false">"By tapping on “Accept”, you consent to the following:\n\nThe app will transmit information it records to the RKI, on a daily basis. The data concerns possible exposures and warnings that have been displayed to you, test results you have retrieved, and whether you have warned other users, and information about your smartphone’s operating system. If you have provided further details above (region, age group), then the RKI will also receive this information.\n\nThe RKI will compile this data into statistics and analyze it to assess the effectiveness and functioning of the app, and draw conclusions regarding the pandemic. The resulting knowledge will help to improve the app’s features and make it more user-friendly, as well as to inform other pandemic response measures.\n\nBefore your data is analyzed, it is necessary to ensure that each app that shares data is only counted once, so as not to distort the statistics. This is why the authenticity of your app needs to be verified. For this purpose, a unique identifier is generated by your smartphone and transmitted to Google in the U.S. or other third countries, so that Google can confirm the authenticity of your app to the RKI. The identifier contains information about the version of your smartphone and the app. On this basis, Google may be able to infer your identity and learn that your smartphone has been authenticated. Google does not receive any other information from the app during this process.\n\nYou can withdraw your consent at any time by disabling the data sharing feature in the app's settings."</string>
 <!-- XTXT: Body point consent for Privacy-preserving Analytics -->
 <string name="ppa_onboarding_privacy_information_point_consent" translatable="false">"Your consent is voluntary. If you do not give your consent, you will still be able to use the app."</string>
 <!-- XTXT: Body point identity for Privacy-preserving Analytics -->
 <string name="ppa_onboarding_privacy_information_point_identity" translatable="false">"If you share data about your use of the app, your identity will still be kept secret from the RKI. This means the RKI will not find out who you are or who you have met. No profiles will be created either."</string>
 <!-- XTXT: Body point sixteen for Privacy-preserving Analytics -->
 <string name="ppa_onboarding_privacy_information_point_sixteen" translatable="false">"You need to be at least 16 years old to give your consent."</string>
 <!-- XHED: Title for Privacy-preserving Analytics additional info  -->
 <string name="ppa_onboarding_more_info_title" translatable="false">"Verification of authenticity and transfer to a third country"</string>
 <!-- XTXT: Body for Privacy-preserving Analytics additional info -->
 <string name="ppa_onboarding_more_info_body" translatable="false">"To confirm the authenticity of your app, your smartphone will generate a unique identifier that contains information about the version of your smartphone and the app. This is necessary to prevent data from being transmitted to the RKI more than once or in an unauthorised manner, as this could distort the results of the analysis. The identifier will be transmitted to Google. This may result in data being transferred to the U.S. or other third countries. There, the level of data protection may not be considered equivalent under European law and it may not be possible to enforce your European data protection rights. In particular, there is a possibility that once the transmitted data reaches Google, it may be accessed and analyzed by security authorities in the third country, even if they have no specific grounds for suspicion, for example by linking the data with other information. This only concerns the identifier sent to Google. Google will not receive the other information about how you use the Corona-Warn-App. It may however be possible for Google to infer your identity from the identifier and learn that your smartphone has been authenticated.\n\nIf you do not consent to this transfer of your data to a third country, please do not tap on “Accept”. You will still be able to use the app, but not the data sharing feature."</string>
 <!-- XTXT: onboarding privacy preserving analytics (ppa) - consent title -->
 <string name="ppa_onboarding_privacy_information_title" translatable="false">"Your Consent"</string>
 <!-- XTXT: Body for Privacy-preserving Analytics settings -->
 <string name="ppa_settings_privacy_information_body" translatable="false">"By enabling “Share Data” above, you consent to the following:\n\nThe app will transmit information it records to the RKI, on a daily basis. The data concerns possible exposures and warnings that have been displayed to you, test results you have retrieved, and whether you have warned other users, and information about your smartphone’s operating system. If you have provided further details above (region, age group), then the RKI will also receive this information.\n\nThe RKI will compile this data into statistics and analyze it to assess the effectiveness and functioning of the app, and draw conclusions regarding the pandemic. The resulting knowledge will help to improve the app’s features and make it more user-friendly, as well as to inform other pandemic response measures.\n\nBefore your data is analyzed, it is necessary to ensure that each app that shares data is only counted once, so as not to distort the statistics. This is why the authenticity of your app needs to be verified. For this purpose, a unique identifier is generated by your smartphone and transmitted to Google in the U.S. or other third countries, so that Google can confirm the authenticity of your app to the RKI. The identifier contains information about the version of your smartphone and the app. On this basis, Google may be able to infer your identity and learn that your smartphone has been authenticated. Google does not receive any other information from the app during this process.\n\n You can withdraw your consent at any time by disabling “Share Data” above."</string>

</resources>
